let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the advantage of CSS? ",
        answer: "A. ability to separate content from presentation",
        options: [
            "A. ability to separate content from presentation",
            "B. ability to provides structure of the web page",
            "C. ability to write a lot of codes to create web page",  
            "D. ability to create visually appealing websites",  
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is CSS for?", 
        answer: "A. to add style to a webpage",
        options: [
            "A. to add style to a webpage",
            "B. to add lines", 
            "C. to make an app",
            "D. to make an appealing design"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the three types of CSS? answer it in the correct order",
        answer: "A. external, internal, and inline",
        options: [
            "A. external, internal, and inline", 
            "B. inline, internal, and external", 
            "C. internal, inline, and external", 
            "D. inline, external, and internal" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "When was CSS created? ",
        answer: "C. 1994",
        options: [
            "A. 1993 ",
            "B. 1991",
            "C. 1994",
            "D. 1992"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Who invented CSS?",
        answer: "D. Hakon Wium Lie and Bert Bos",
        options: [
            "A. Jimmy Wales", 
            "B. Bert Bos", 
            "C. Hakon Wium Lie", 
            "D. Hakon Wium Lie and Bert Bos" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "If you're going to use css, do you believe you do not need to include html attributes? ",
        answer: "A. Yes",
        options: [
            "A. Yes", 
            "B. No", 
            "C. Maybe", 
            "D. Strongly not" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "How to make a global change in CSS? ",
        answer: "D. All of the above",
        options: [
            "A. Change the style", 
            "B. Brainstorm", 
            "C. Be artistic", 
            "D. All of the above" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How many versions CSS have? ",
        answer: "C. 3",
        options: [
            "A. 1",
            "B. 2",
            "C. 3",
            "D. 4"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What version of CSS is the oldest?",
        answer: "D. 1996",
        options: [
            "A. 1993",
            "B. 1995",
            "C. 1994",
            "D. 1996"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What version of CSS is most used today? ",
        answer: "C. CSS3",
        options: [
            "A. CSS1", 
            "B. CSS2", 
            "C. CSS3", 
            "D. CSS4"            

        ]
    },
]